intact | seated 0/0 | piece -1 Welded | simulation 0.000s
cracked | seated 0/0 | piece -1 Welded | simulation 0.013s
fractured | seated 0/0 | piece -1 Welded | simulation 0.380s
repair | seated 0/40 | piece 39 Captured | simulation 0.393s
repair | seated 0/40 | piece 39 Captured | simulation 0.493s
repair | seated 0/40 | piece 39 Captured | simulation 0.593s
repair | seated 0/40 | piece 39 Captured | simulation 0.693s
repair | seated 0/40 | piece 39 Aligning | simulation 0.793s
repair | seated 1/40 | piece 25 Captured | simulation 0.893s
repair | seated 1/40 | piece 25 Captured | simulation 0.993s
repair | seated 1/40 | piece 25 Captured | simulation 1.093s
repair | seated 1/40 | piece 25 Captured | simulation 1.193s
repair | seated 2/40 | piece 31 Captured | simulation 1.293s
repair | seated 2/40 | piece 31 Captured | simulation 1.393s
repair | seated 2/40 | piece 31 Captured | simulation 1.493s
repair | seated 2/40 | piece 31 Captured | simulation 1.593s
repair | seated 2/40 | piece 31 Captured | simulation 1.693s
repair | seated 3/40 | piece 33 Captured | simulation 1.793s
repair | seated 3/40 | piece 33 Captured | simulation 1.893s
repair | seated 3/40 | piece 33 Captured | simulation 1.993s
repair | seated 3/40 | piece 33 Captured | simulation 2.093s
repair | seated 3/40 | piece 33 Captured | simulation 2.193s
repair | seated 4/40 | piece 16 Captured | simulation 2.293s
repair | seated 4/40 | piece 16 Captured | simulation 2.393s
repair | seated 4/40 | piece 16 Captured | simulation 2.493s
repair | seated 4/40 | piece 16 Captured | simulation 2.593s
repair | seated 4/40 | piece 16 Captured | simulation 2.693s
repair | seated 5/40 | piece 0 Captured | simulation 2.793s
repair | seated 5/40 | piece 0 Captured | simulation 2.893s
repair | seated 5/40 | piece 0 Captured | simulation 2.993s
repair | seated 5/40 | piece 0 Captured | simulation 3.093s
repair | seated 5/40 | piece 0 Captured | simulation 3.193s
repair | seated 6/40 | piece 11 Captured | simulation 3.293s
repair | seated 6/40 | piece 11 Captured | simulation 3.393s
repair | seated 6/40 | piece 11 Captured | simulation 3.493s
repair | seated 6/40 | piece 11 Captured | simulation 3.593s
repair | seated 6/40 | piece 11 Captured | simulation 3.693s
repair | seated 7/40 | piece 2 Captured | simulation 3.793s
repair | seated 7/40 | piece 2 Captured | simulation 3.893s
repair | seated 7/40 | piece 2 Captured | simulation 3.993s
repair | seated 7/40 | piece 2 Captured | simulation 4.093s
repair | seated 7/40 | piece 2 Captured | simulation 4.193s
repair | seated 8/40 | piece 29 Captured | simulation 4.293s
repair | seated 8/40 | piece 29 Captured | simulation 4.393s
repair | seated 8/40 | piece 29 Captured | simulation 4.493s
repair | seated 8/40 | piece 29 Captured | simulation 4.593s
repair | seated 8/40 | piece 29 Captured | simulation 4.693s
repair | seated 9/40 | piece 9 Captured | simulation 4.793s
repair | seated 9/40 | piece 9 Captured | simulation 4.893s
repair | seated 9/40 | piece 9 Captured | simulation 4.993s
repair | seated 9/40 | piece 9 Captured | simulation 5.093s
repair | seated 9/40 | piece 9 Captured | simulation 5.193s
repair | seated 10/40 | piece 22 Captured | simulation 5.293s
repair | seated 10/40 | piece 22 Captured | simulation 5.393s
repair | seated 10/40 | piece 22 Captured | simulation 5.493s
repair | seated 10/40 | piece 22 Captured | simulation 5.613s
repair | seated 10/40 | piece 22 Aligning | simulation 5.733s
repair | seated 11/40 | piece 18 Captured | simulation 5.853s
repair | seated 11/40 | piece 18 Captured | simulation 5.973s
repair | seated 11/40 | piece 18 Captured | simulation 6.093s
repair | seated 11/40 | piece 18 Aligning | simulation 6.193s
repair | seated 12/40 | piece 4 Captured | simulation 6.313s
repair | seated 12/40 | piece 4 Captured | simulation 6.433s
repair | seated 12/40 | piece 4 Captured | simulation 6.553s
repair | seated 12/40 | piece 4 Captured | simulation 6.673s
repair | seated 13/40 | piece 6 Captured | simulation 6.793s
repair | seated 13/40 | piece 6 Captured | simulation 6.913s
repair | seated 13/40 | piece 6 Captured | simulation 7.013s
repair | seated 13/40 | piece 6 Captured | simulation 7.133s
repair | seated 14/40 | piece 24 Captured | simulation 7.253s
repair | seated 14/40 | piece 24 Captured | simulation 7.373s
repair | seated 14/40 | piece 24 Captured | simulation 7.493s
repair | seated 14/40 | piece 24 Captured | simulation 7.613s
repair | seated 14/40 | piece 24 Aligning | simulation 7.733s
repair | seated 15/40 | piece 27 Captured | simulation 7.833s
repair | seated 15/40 | piece 27 Captured | simulation 7.953s
repair | seated 15/40 | piece 27 Captured | simulation 8.073s
repair | seated 15/40 | piece 27 Captured | simulation 8.193s
repair | seated 16/40 | piece 35 Captured | simulation 8.313s
repair | seated 16/40 | piece 35 Captured | simulation 8.433s
repair | seated 16/40 | piece 35 Captured | simulation 8.533s
repair | seated 16/40 | piece 35 Captured | simulation 8.653s
repair | seated 16/40 | piece 35 Aligning | simulation 8.773s
repair | seated 17/40 | piece 32 Captured | simulation 8.893s
repair | seated 17/40 | piece 32 Captured | simulation 9.013s
repair | seated 17/40 | piece 32 Captured | simulation 9.133s
repair | seated 17/40 | piece 32 Aligning | simulation 9.253s
repair | seated 18/40 | piece 13 Captured | simulation 9.353s
repair | seated 18/40 | piece 13 Captured | simulation 9.473s
repair | seated 18/40 | piece 13 Captured | simulation 9.593s
repair | seated 18/40 | piece 13 Captured | simulation 9.713s
repair | seated 19/40 | piece 15 Captured | simulation 9.833s
repair | seated 19/40 | piece 15 Captured | simulation 9.953s
repair | seated 19/40 | piece 15 Captured | simulation 10.073s
repair | seated 19/40 | piece 15 Captured | simulation 10.173s
repair | seated 19/40 | piece 15 Aligning | simulation 10.293s
repair | seated 20/40 | piece 37 Captured | simulation 10.413s
repair | seated 20/40 | piece 37 Captured | simulation 10.533s
repair | seated 20/40 | piece 37 Captured | simulation 10.653s
repair | seated 20/40 | piece 37 Aligning | simulation 10.773s
repair | seated 21/40 | piece 17 Captured | simulation 10.893s
repair | seated 21/40 | piece 17 Captured | simulation 10.993s
repair | seated 21/40 | piece 17 Captured | simulation 11.113s
repair | seated 21/40 | piece 17 Captured | simulation 11.233s
repair | seated 22/40 | piece 20 Captured | simulation 11.353s
repair | seated 22/40 | piece 20 Captured | simulation 11.473s
repair | seated 22/40 | piece 20 Captured | simulation 11.593s
repair | seated 22/40 | piece 20 Captured | simulation 11.713s
repair | seated 23/40 | piece 1 Captured | simulation 11.813s
repair | seated 23/40 | piece 1 Captured | simulation 11.933s
repair | seated 23/40 | piece 1 Captured | simulation 12.053s
repair | seated 23/40 | piece 1 Captured | simulation 12.173s
repair | seated 23/40 | piece 1 Aligning | simulation 12.293s
repair | seated 24/40 | piece 19 Captured | simulation 12.413s
repair | seated 24/40 | piece 19 Captured | simulation 12.513s
repair | seated 24/40 | piece 19 Captured | simulation 12.633s
repair | seated 24/40 | piece 19 Captured | simulation 12.753s
repair | seated 25/40 | piece 3 Captured | simulation 12.873s
repair | seated 25/40 | piece 3 Captured | simulation 12.993s
repair | seated 25/40 | piece 3 Captured | simulation 13.113s
repair | seated 25/40 | piece 3 Captured | simulation 13.233s
repair | seated 25/40 | piece 3 Aligning | simulation 13.333s
repair | seated 26/40 | piece 10 Captured | simulation 13.433s
repair | seated 26/40 | piece 10 Captured | simulation 13.553s
repair | seated 26/40 | piece 10 Captured | simulation 13.653s
repair | seated 26/40 | piece 10 Captured | simulation 13.753s
repair | seated 27/40 | piece 8 Captured | simulation 13.873s
repair | seated 27/40 | piece 8 Captured | simulation 13.973s
repair | seated 27/40 | piece 8 Captured | simulation 14.073s
repair | seated 27/40 | piece 8 Captured | simulation 14.173s
repair | seated 27/40 | piece 8 Captured | simulation 14.293s
repair | seated 28/40 | piece 7 Captured | simulation 14.393s
repair | seated 28/40 | piece 7 Captured | simulation 14.493s
repair | seated 28/40 | piece 7 Captured | simulation 14.613s
repair | seated 28/40 | piece 7 Captured | simulation 14.713s
repair | seated 28/40 | piece 7 Captured | simulation 14.813s
repair | seated 29/40 | piece 28 Captured | simulation 14.913s
repair | seated 29/40 | piece 28 Captured | simulation 15.033s
repair | seated 29/40 | piece 28 Captured | simulation 15.133s
repair | seated 29/40 | piece 28 Captured | simulation 15.233s
repair | seated 29/40 | piece 28 Aligning | simulation 15.353s
repair | seated 30/40 | piece 12 Captured | simulation 15.453s
repair | seated 30/40 | piece 12 Captured | simulation 15.553s
repair | seated 30/40 | piece 12 Captured | simulation 15.673s
repair | seated 30/40 | piece 12 Captured | simulation 15.773s
repair | seated 31/40 | piece 30 Captured | simulation 15.873s
repair | seated 31/40 | piece 30 Captured | simulation 15.973s
repair | seated 31/40 | piece 30 Captured | simulation 16.093s
repair | seated 31/40 | piece 30 Captured | simulation 16.193s
repair | seated 31/40 | piece 30 Captured | simulation 16.293s
repair | seated 32/40 | piece 38 Captured | simulation 16.413s
repair | seated 32/40 | piece 38 Captured | simulation 16.513s
repair | seated 32/40 | piece 38 Captured | simulation 16.613s
repair | seated 32/40 | piece 38 Captured | simulation 16.713s
repair | seated 32/40 | piece 38 Aligning | simulation 16.833s
repair | seated 33/40 | piece 23 Captured | simulation 16.933s
repair | seated 33/40 | piece 23 Captured | simulation 17.033s
repair | seated 33/40 | piece 23 Captured | simulation 17.153s
repair | seated 33/40 | piece 23 Captured | simulation 17.253s
repair | seated 33/40 | piece 23 Aligning | simulation 17.353s
repair | seated 34/40 | piece 14 Captured | simulation 17.453s
repair | seated 34/40 | piece 14 Captured | simulation 17.573s
repair | seated 34/40 | piece 14 Captured | simulation 17.673s
repair | seated 34/40 | piece 14 Captured | simulation 17.773s
repair | seated 35/40 | piece 36 Captured | simulation 17.893s
repair | seated 35/40 | piece 36 Captured | simulation 17.993s
repair | seated 35/40 | piece 36 Captured | simulation 18.093s
repair | seated 35/40 | piece 36 Captured | simulation 18.193s
repair | seated 35/40 | piece 36 Captured | simulation 18.313s
repair | seated 36/40 | piece 26 Captured | simulation 18.413s
repair | seated 36/40 | piece 26 Captured | simulation 18.513s
repair | seated 36/40 | piece 26 Captured | simulation 18.633s
repair | seated 36/40 | piece 26 Captured | simulation 18.733s
repair | seated 36/40 | piece 26 Aligning | simulation 18.833s
repair | seated 37/40 | piece 34 Captured | simulation 18.933s
repair | seated 37/40 | piece 34 Captured | simulation 19.053s
repair | seated 37/40 | piece 34 Captured | simulation 19.153s
repair | seated 37/40 | piece 34 Captured | simulation 19.253s
repair | seated 37/40 | piece 34 Aligning | simulation 19.373s
repair | seated 38/40 | piece 5 Captured | simulation 19.473s
repair | seated 38/40 | piece 5 Captured | simulation 19.573s
repair | seated 38/40 | piece 5 Captured | simulation 19.673s
repair | seated 38/40 | piece 5 Captured | simulation 19.793s
repair | seated 38/40 | piece 5 Aligning | simulation 19.893s
repair | seated 39/40 | piece 21 Captured | simulation 19.993s
repair | seated 39/40 | piece 21 Captured | simulation 20.113s
repair | seated 39/40 | piece 21 Captured | simulation 20.213s
repair | seated 39/40 | piece 21 Captured | simulation 20.313s
repair | seated 40/40 | piece -1 Welded | simulation 20.433s
complete | seated 40/40 | piece -1 Welded | simulation 20.433s